Guide to the Walter Chauncey Camp Papers
Yale University. Department of Manuscripts and Archives
- Correspondence, 1875 - 1925; Series I; 13 linear feet (31 boxes)
  - Cochran, Guy Hunt, 1895, undated (Box 5, Folder 155)
  - Cochran, Thomas, Jr., 1917 (Box 5, Folder 155)
  - Cochrane, A. D., [1902?] (Box 5, Folder 155)
  - Cochrane, Dewitt, 1909 (Box 5, Folder 155)
  - Cochrane, J. Sullivan, 1911 (Box 5, Folder 155)
  - Codman, John, 1895 (Box 5, Folder 156)
  - Coe College, 1894, 1902 (Box 5, Folder 156)
  - Coe, Franklin
  - Coe, W. T., 1919 (Box 5, Folder 156)
  - Coffin, Harry R., 1905, 1911, 1919-1920 (Box 5, Folder 157)
  - Coffin, Seward V.(*), 1889, 1891-1893, 1900, 1905 (Box 5, Folder 157)
  - Coffman, B. Nelson(*), 1913-1917, 1919-1923 (Box 5, Folder 158)
  - Colby, Bainbridge, 1920 (Box 5, Folder 159)
  - Colgate Academy, 1894 (Box 5, Folder 159)
  - Colgate & Company, 1917-1920 (Box 5, Folder 159)
  - Colgate, Richard M., 1909 (Box 5, Folder 159)
  - Colgate University, 1908, 1917 (Box 5, Folder 159)
  - College Athlete, 1899-1900 (Box 5, Folder 160)
  - College Year - Book, 1899 (Box 5, Folder 160)
  - Collier, Barron G., 1919 (Box 6, Folder 161)
  - Collier, George L., 1894 (Box 6, Folder 161)
  - Collier, Harris, 1894 (Box 6, Folder 161)
  - Collier, Robert J., 1899, 1910, 1917, undated (Box 6, Folder 161)
  - Collier's Weekly (*), 1889-1902 (Box 6, Folder 162-181)
  - Collier's Weekly, 1902-1924, undated (Box 7, Folder 182-194)
  - Colonial Motion Picture Corporation, 1914 (Box 7, Folder 195)
  - Colorado State School of Mines, 1900 (Box 7, Folder 195)
  - Colorado, University of, 1902, 1915 (Box 7, Folder 195)
  - Coloroto Corporation, 1924 (Box 7, Folder 195)
  - Columbia (South Carolina) State College, 1921 (Box 7, Folder 195)
  - Columbia University, 1902 (Box 7, Folder 195)
  - Colwell, Percy Robert, 1906 (Box 7, Folder 195)
  - Comery, Edgar, 1911 (Box 7, Folder 196)
  - Committee of Civic & Social Service, 1920 (Box 7, Folder 196)
  - Community Baseball Association, 1916 (Box 7, Folder 196)
  - Community Service, 1920-1921, 1923 (Box 7, Folder 196)
    Includes a report of first year of War Camp Community Service activities.
  - Congregationalist, 1911-1912 (Box 7, Folder 197)
  - Conibear, H. B., 1911 (Box 7, Folder 197)
  - Conner, William W., 1894 (Box 7, Folder 197)
  - Connolly, J. B., 1899 (Box 7, Folder 197)
  - Conover, J. P., 1894, 1909 (Box 7, Folder 197)
  - Consolidated Press(*), 1920-1924, undated (Box 7, Folder 198-201)
  - Cook, A. D., 1902 (Box 7, Folder 202)
  - Cook, Arthur, 1914 (Box 7, Folder 202)
  - Cook, R. J., 1899, 1911, undated (Box 7, Folder 202)
  - Cook, W. J., 1894 (Box 7, Folder 202)
  - Cooke & Fry, 1900 (Box 7, Folder 202)
  - Coolidge, Archibald Cary, 1904-1905 (Box 7, Folder 203)
  - Coolidge, T. J., Jr., [1888], undated (Box 7, Folder 203)
  - Cooper, Vaughn W., 1911 (Box 7, Folder 203)
  - Corbett, James J., 1897 (Box 7, Folder 204)
  - Corbett, John P., 1916 (Box 7, Folder 204)
  - Corbin, William Herbert(*), 1888-1913, undated (Box 7, Folder 204)
  - Cornelius, Benjamin F., Jr., undated (Box 7, Folder 205)
  - Cornelius S. Bushnell Nat'1 (Box 7, Folder 205)
  - Memorial Association, 1900 (Box 7, Folder 205)
  - Cornell University, 1889-1908 (Box 7, Folder 205)
  - Corn Exchange Nat'l Bank, 1923 (Box 7, Folder 205)
  - Cornwell, Charles H., 1903 (Box 7, Folder 206)
  - Cornwell, Frank S., 1917, 1922 (Box 7, Folder 206)
  - Cornwell, William C., 1896 (Box 7, Folder 206)
  - Cortelyou, George B., Jr., 1923 (Box 7, Folder 206)
  - Corwin, Robert Nelson(*), 1886-1917 (Box 8, Folder 207)
    See also: box 29, folder 799-803
  - Cosby, Arthur Fortunatus, 1918 (Box 8, Folder 208)
  - Cosmopolitan Magazine, 1909 (Box 8, Folder 208)
  - Coss, Clyde K., 1916, 1919 (Box 8, Folder 208)
  - Costello, Harry(*), 1919-1922 (Box 8, Folder 208)
  - Cotton, Arthur N., 1908 (Box 8, Folder 209)
  - Cotton, W. J., 1894, 1922 (Box 8, Folder 209)
  - Counselman, J. S., 1913 (Box 8, Folder 209)
  - Country Life in America, 1912 (Box 8, Folder 209)
  - Courleux, Ferdinand J., 1911, 1916 (Box 8, Folder 209)
  - Coursen, W. A., 1911 (Box 8, Folder 209)
  - Courtney, Charles E., [1902?], 1912 (Box 8, Folder 209)
  - Coutchie, J. G., 1922 (Box 8, Folder 209)
  - Covington, J. Harry, 1917-1918 (Box 8, Folder 210)
  - Cowan, H. W., 1894 (Box 8, Folder 210)
  - Cowles, R. A., 1895, 1899-1900 (Box 8, Folder 210)
  - Cowles, W. G., 1899 (Box 8, Folder 210)
  - Cowles, W. H., 1908 (Box 8, Folder 210)
  - Cox, James T., 1905 (Box 8, Folder 211)
  - Cox, Thomas, 1900 (Box 8, Folder 211)
  - Coxe, Macgrane, 1917 (Box 8, Folder 211)
  - Coy, E. H., 1909, 1919 (Box 8, Folder 212)
  - Coy, Edward G., 1894, 1901 (Box 8, Folder 212)
  - Coy, Nathan B., 1900, 1909 (Box 8, Folder 212)
  - Coy, Ted, [1919], 1920 (Box 8, Folder 212)
  - Coyle, Francis L., 1895 (Box 8, Folder 212)
  - Crabtree, J. W., 1909 (Box 8, Folder 213)
  - Crandall, Ben, 1900 (Box 8, Folder 213)
  - Crane, A. G., 1923 (Box 8, Folder 213)
  - Crane, Edwin R., 1894 (Box 8, Folder 213)
  - Crane, Joshua, 1907 (Box 8, Folder 213)
  - Cranston, John L., 1894 (Box 8, Folder 213)
  - Craver, Forrest E., 1905 (Box 8, Folder 213)
  - Crawford, Henry J., 1901 (Box 8, Folder 213)
  - Crawford, William H., 1920 (Box 8, Folder 213)
  - Crescent Athletic Club, Brooklyn (New York), 1917 (Box 8, Folder 214)
  - Crescent Club, St. Louis, 1906 (Box 8, Folder 214)
  - Critchlow, G. Clayton, 1902 (Box 8, Folder 214)
  - Crocker, Adams, 1884 (Box 8, Folder 214)
  - Crocker, William H., 1915, 1924 (Box 8, Folder 214)
  - Cronyn, Hume, 1888-1890 (Box 8, Folder 214)
  - Crosby, Albert W., 1917 (Box 8, Folder 215)
  - Crosby, Oscar T., 1917 (Box 8, Folder 215)
  - Crosby, Stephen J. R., 1893-1995, 1907, 1911 (Box 8, Folder 215)
  - Cross, Albert, undated (Box 8, Folder 216)
  - Cross, Harry P., 1896, 1917, 1919 (Box 8, Folder 216)
  - Cross, S. M., 1893 (Box 8, Folder 216)
  - Crowdis, Edwin G., 1894 (Box 8, Folder 216)
  - Crowe, John M., 1892 (Box 8, Folder 216)
  - Crowell (Thomas Y.) Co., 1919-1920 (Box 8, Folder 216)
  - Crowningshield, Frank, 1920 (Box 8, Folder 216)
    See also: box 25, folder 719
  - Crowther, Samuel, 1915 (Box 8, Folder 216)
  - Cryder, Henry Chauncey, 1897 (Box 8, Folder 216)
  - Cullman, Howard S., 1920 (Box 8, Folder 217)
  - Cummings, Frank A., 1920 (Box 8, Folder 217)
  - Cumnock, A. J., 1889, 1890, undated (Box 8, Folder 217)
  - Cuntz, J. H., 1900 (Box 8, Folder 217)
  - Curley, James M., 1917 (Box 8, Folder 217)
  - Curley, W. T., 1900 (Box 8, Folder 217)
  - Current News Features, Inc., 1924 (Box 8, Folder 218)
  - Curtis Feature Service, 1916 (Box 8, Folder 218)
  - Curtis, Julian W.
    See: box 1, folder 22 See: box 23, folder 640-647 See: box 29, folder 808-812
  - Curtis, O. Marcus, 1894 (Box 8, Folder 218)
  - Curtis Publishing Company, 1912 (Box 8, Folder 218)
  - Curtis, W. P., 1911 (Box 8, Folder 218)
  - Curtiss, F. Homer, 1906 (Box 8, Folder 218)
  - Cush, Walter J., 1894 (Box 8, Folder 219)
  - Cushing, Harvey, 1916 (Box 8, Folder 219)
  - Cushing, J. P., 1902 (Box 8, Folder 219)
  - Cushing, L., 1878 (Box 8, Folder 219)
  - Cushing, W. H., 1916 (Box 8, Folder 219)
  - Cushing, W. L., 1892, 1894, 1908 (Box 8, Folder 219)
  - Cutcheon, Fred R. M., 1903 (Box 8, Folder 219)
  - Cutler, Arthur H., 1894, 1896 (Box 8, Folder 219)
  - Cutler, John W., Jr., 1921 (Box 8, Folder 219)
  - Cutts, Oliver F., 1914 (Box 8, Folder 219)
  - Cuyler, C. C.(*), 1891-1907 (Box 8, Folder 220-221)
  - Cuyler, Thomas DeWitt(*), 1893-1920 (Box 8, Folder 222)
  - Cuzzort, Belva, undated (Box 8, Folder 222)
  - Daggett, David, 1901, 1911, 1914 (Box 8, Folder 223)
  - Daggett, Leonard M., 1905, 1917 (Box 8, Folder 223)
  - Dailey, Vincent, 1910 (Box 8, Folder 223)
  - Daily Dozen(*), 1917-1923, undated (Box 8, Folder 224-230)
  - Dale, Norman, 1911 (Box 8, Folder 231)
  - Daley, G. Herbert, 1907, 1913-1914, 1916 (Box 8, Folder 231)
  - Dallas News, 1916 (Box 8, Folder 231)
  - Dallas, Samuel J., 1918 (Box 8, Folder 231)
  - Daly, Charles Dudley, 1899-1900,1919 (Box 8, Folder 231)
  - Daly, Fred J., 1910 (Box 8, Folder 231)
  - Dalzell, William J., 1892-1893, 1900, 1907, 1917 (Box 8, Folder 231)
  - Dana, Arnold G., 1902 (Box 8, Folder 232)
  - Dana, Jesse D., 1900, 1917 (Box 8, Folder 232)
  - Dana, R. H., 1902 (Box 8, Folder 232)
  - Danbury Parent - Teacher Ass'n., 1923 (Box 8, Folder 232)
  - Danforth, G. H., 1902 (Box 8, Folder 232)
  - Daniels, Josephus(*), 1917-1919, undated (Box 8, Folder 233)
  - Daniels, Lee E., undated (Box 8, Folder 233)
  - Daniels, M. Grant, 1894 (Box 8, Folder 233)
  - Dann, Jesse C., [1889?] (Box 8, Folder 233)
  - Darlington High School, 1916 (Box 9, Folder 234)
  - Dartmouth College(*), 1884, 1904-1905, 1913, 1920, undated (Box 9, Folder 234)
  - Dashiel, Paul(*), 1892-1920, undated (Box 9, Folder 235)
  - Davidson, Homer H., 1903 (Box 9, Folder 236)
  - Davidson, John Russell, 1900 (Box 9, Folder 236)
  - Davies, Joseph E., 1917 (Box 9, Folder 236)
  - Davis, Frank H., 1922 (Box 9, Folder 236)
  - Davis, H. B., 1893 (Box 9, Folder 236)
  - Davis, H. C., 1894 (Box 9, Folder 236)
  - Davis, John W., 1917 (Box 9, Folder 236)
  - Davis, K. E.(*), 1910, 1914, 1917, 1922, undated (Box 9, Folder 236)
  - Davis, Parke H.(*), 1894-1911 (Box 9, Folder 237)
  - Davis, Parke H.(*), 1912-1920 (Box 9, Folder 238)
  - Davis, Richard Harding, [1901], 1902, 1913, undated (Box 9, Folder 239)
  - Dawson, Fred G., 1911 (Box 9, Folder 239)
  - Day, George Parmley
    See: box 22, folder 613-620 See: box 28, folder 792 See: box 30, folder 835
  - Deffenbaugh, J. M., 1892 (Box 9, Folder 239)
  - De Gaulles, John R., 1908-1909 (Box 9, Folder 239)
  - Deland, Lorin(*), 1894-1910, undated (Box 9, Folder 240)
  - Delano, Frederic, 1917 (Box 9, Folder 241)
  - Delano, Moreau, 1919 (Box 9, Folder 241)
  - Delany, William S., 1905 (Box 9, Folder 241)
  - Delineator, 1922 (Box 9, Folder 242)
  - Delta Kappa Epsilon Fraternity, 1892, 1904, 1909,1923-1924, undated (Box 9, Folder 242)
  - Deming, John C., 1920-1921 (Box 9, Folder 242)
  - Denison, Robert C., 1916-1917 (Box 9, Folder 243)
  - Denman, William, 1893, 1917 (Box 9, Folder 243)
  - Dennis, Frank L., 1919 (Box 9, Folder 243)
  - Dennis, L. M.(*), 1896-1912 (Box 9, Folder 244-245)
  - Derby, Richard, 1901-1902, 1918 (Box 9, Folder 246)
  - Deseret News, 1909 (Box 9, Folder 246)
  - De Shon, Charles G., Jr., 1903 (Box 9, Folder 246)
  - de Sibour, Henri, [1895] (Box 9, Folder 246)
  - Des Moines Capital, 1923 (Box 9, Folder 246)
  - Des Moines Register, 1916 (Box 9, Folder 246)
  - Detroit College, 1899 (Box 9, Folder 246)
  - Detroit District Golf Ass'n., 1924 (Box 9, Folder 246)
  - Deutsch, Henry, 1922 (Box 9, Folder 247)
  - Devereux, H. K., 1893 (Box 9, Folder 247)
  - DeWaltoff, S. A, 1923 (Box 9, Folder 247)
  - Dewey, J. Hiland, 1894 (Box 9, Folder 247)
  - de Witt, John, 1912, undated (Box 9, Folder 247)
  - Dexter, E. G., 1903 (Box 9, Folder 247)
  - Dexter, Morton, 1908 (Box 9, Folder 247)
  - Dickinson College, 1899, 1909 (Box 9, Folder 248)
  - Dickler, Nathan N., 1913 (Box 9, Folder 248)
  - Dittrich, Ben, 1900 (Box 9, Folder 248)
  - Dobie, Gilmour, 1916 (Box 9, Folder 249)
  - Dodd, Mead & Company, 1912, 1917 (Box 9, Folder 249)
  - Dodge Publishing Company, 1915 (Box 9, Folder 249)
  - Dodson, E., 1919 (Box 9, Folder 249)
  - Dole, Charles S., 1896 (Box 9, Folder 249)
  - Dole, George S., 1909 (Box 9, Folder 249)
  - Donahue, Michael J., 1909-1921 (Box 9, Folder 250)
  - Donnelley (R. R.) & Sons Co., 1896 (Box 9, Folder 250)
  - Donnelley (Reuben H.) Corp., 1919 (Box 9, Folder 250)
  - Donnelly, Charles F., 1911 (Box 9, Folder 250)
  - Donnelly, E. J., 1907 (Box 9, Folder 250)
  - Dorsey, Hugh M., 1917 (Box 9, Folder 250)
  - Doubleday, Page & Company(*), 1901-1924, undated (Box 9, Folder 251-253)
  - Dougherty, Henry E., 1914 (Box 9, Folder 254)
  - Douglas, Hamilton, Jr., 1910 (Box 9, Folder 254)
  - Douglas, R. F., 1910 (Box 9, Folder 254)
  - Douglas, W. B., 1888 (Box 9, Folder 254)
  - Downer, W. V., 1894, 1905 (Box 9, Folder 255)
  - Downes (E. J.) & Company, [1891] (Box 9, Folder 255)
  - Downing, E. V., 1900 (Box 9, Folder 255)
  - Downing, P. M., 1894 (Box 9, Folder 255)
  - Doyle, Charles M., 1899 (Box 9, Folder 255)
  - Doyle, Hartley J., 1923 (Box 9, Folder 255)
  - Doyle, John Hadley, 1899 (Box 9, Folder 255)
  - Drake University, 1923-1924 (Box 9, Folder 256)
  - Draper, Anna Palmer, undated (Box 9, Folder 256)
  - Dray, Walter R., 1910 (Box 9, Folder 256)
  - Dresden International Hygienic Exposition, 1911 (Box 9, Folder 256)
  - Drew, Putnam, 1907 (Box 9, Folder 256)
  - Drinker, Henry S., 1905 (Box 9, Folder 256)
  - Ducournan, John A., 1911 (Box 9, Folder 257)
  - Dudley, Albertus, 1904 (Box 9, Folder 257)
  - Dudley, John K., 1922 (Box 9, Folder 257)
  - Dudley, William L., 1894, 1910-1911 (Box 9, Folder 257)
  - Dull, A. P. L., 1892 (Box 9, Folder 257)
  - Dunbar, Noel S, 1914 (Box 9, Folder 258)
  - Duncan, Jeptha B., 1903 (Box 9, Folder 258)
  - Dunham, C. P., 1899 (Box 9, Folder 258)
  - Dunham, C. T., 1902 (Box 9, Folder 258)
  - Dunlap, Alva, 1922 (Box 9, Folder 258)
  - Dunn, Harry W., 1898-1899 (Box 9, Folder 258)
  - Dunroven, _______, 1893, undated (Box 9, Folder 258)
  - Dupont, Coleman, 1919 (Box 9, Folder 259)
  - Durand, Henry S., 1897 (Box 9, Folder 259)
  - Durant, E. W., 1924 (Box 9, Folder 259)
  - Durston, W. H., 1899 (Box 9, Folder 259)
  - Duval, C. Livingston, undated (Box 9, Folder 259)
  - Dwight, Timothy, 1892, 1894, 1898 (Box 9, Folder 259)
  - Dysart Hotel, 1907 (Box 9, Folder 259)
  - Eadie, Robert, 1900 (Box 10, Folder 260)
  - Early, J. L. Evering, 1916 (Box 10, Folder 260)
  - East Orange (New Jersey) High School, 1919 (Box 10, Folder 260)
  - Eaton, O. V., 1895-1896 (Box 10, Folder 260)
  - Eavenson, Howard N., 1924 (Box 10, Folder 260)
  - Eckersall, Walter H., 1907 (Box 10, Folder 261)
  - Eddy, R. Condit, 1894 (Box 10, Folder 261)
  - Edinger, F. G., 1894 (Box 10, Folder 261)
  - Edmonds, Leslie E., 1916 (Box 10, Folder 261)
  - Edwards, Duncan, 1889-1891 (Box 10, Folder 262)
  - Edwards, George C., 1902 (Box 10, Folder 262)
  - Edwards, William H., 1908, 1916, 1921 (Box 10, Folder 262)
  - Edwards, W. O., Jr., 1894 (Box 10, Folder 262)
  - Edwin Bancroft Foote Boys' Club, 1906 (Box 10, Folder 262)
  - Effron, Matilda E., 1916 (Box 10, Folder 263)
  - Ehler, George W., 1905, 1910, 1915 (Box 10, Folder 263)
  - Elcock, Walter B., 1920 (Box 10, Folder 263)
  - Elder, Samuel J.(*), 1893-1898, 1905-1917 (Box 10, Folder 264-265)
  - Eldred, George, 1905 (Box 10, Folder 266)
  - Eldridge, Frederick L, 1894 (Box 10, Folder 266)
  - Eliot, Charles W., Undated,[1910] (Box 10, Folder 266)
  - Ellis, George W., 1911 (Box 10, Folder 266)
  - Ellis, Kimpton, 1924 (Box 10, Folder 266)
  - Emmerich, F. J., 1923 (Box 10, Folder 267)
  - Emmett, O. B., 1911 (Box 10, Folder 267)
  - Emmons, Robert W., 1894 (Box 10, Folder 267)
  - Empie, Adam, 1919 (Box 10, Folder 267)
  - Emrick, F. G., 1919-1921 (Box 10, Folder 267)
  - Encyclopedia Britannica(*), 1899-1900, 1904, 1911 (Box 10, Folder 268)
  - Engin, D., 1907 (Box 10, Folder 268)
  - English, Philip, 1909 (Box 10, Folder 268)
  - Ernst, Roger, 1905 (Box 10, Folder 268)
  - Ervine, William, 1893 (Box 10, Folder 268)
  - Esrey, Earl D., 1909 (Box 10, Folder 268)
  - Evening Bulletin (Philadelphia), 1917-1918 (Box 10, Folder 269)
  - Evening Post (Hartford), 1889 (Box 10, Folder 269)
  - Evening Post (New York City), 1918 (Box 10, Folder 269)
  - Evening Wisconsin, 1906 (Box 10, Folder 269)
  - Everett, William, 1894 (Box 10, Folder 269)
  - Exposition Committee of the Sportsman's Association, 1896 (Box 10, Folder 269)
  - Eyre, Alfred S., 1898-1902(*) (Box 10, Folder 270)
  - Fairchild, Edwin Milton, 1905-1906, 1913, undated (Box 10, Folder 271)
  - Farley, G. Wells, 1900 (Box 10, Folder 271)
  - Farmer, Allen B., 1914-1915 (Box 10, Folder 271)
  - Farnam, C. H., 1889 (Box 10, Folder 272)
  - Farnam, Henry W.
    See: box 22, folder 613-620
  - Farnam, John D., 1896 (Box 10, Folder 272)
    See also: box 22, folder 613-620
  - Farnsworth, Fred B.
  - Farrell, Edward L., 1918 (Box 10, Folder 273)
  - Farrier, A. M., 1916 (Box 10, Folder 273)
  - Farwell, John V., 1894, 1911 (Box 10, Folder 273)
  - Faucon, Gorham F., 1893-1894 (Box 10, Folder 274)
  - Faunce, W. H. P., 1916 (Box 10, Folder 274)
  - Fawcett, Roscoe, 1911, 1914 (Box 10, Folder 274)
  - Fearing, George R., 1894 (Box 10, Folder 275)
  - Feasley, Milton, 1923 (Box 10, Folder 275)
  - Fédération Internationale de Boxe Amateur, undated (Box 10, Folder 275)
  - Fell, A. G., 1894 (Box 10, Folder 275)
  - Fennell, D. T., 1909 (Box 10, Folder 275)
  - Fergin, A. H., 1899 (Box 10, Folder 276)
  - Ferry, Charles H., 1901 (Box 10, Folder 276)
  - Ferry, Mansfield, 1900 (Box 10, Folder 276)
  - Fess, Lowell, 1916 (Box 10, Folder 276)
  - Field, James A., 1901 (Box 10, Folder 277)
  - Field, John W., 1911, 1916 (Box 10, Folder 277)
  - Field, Sally Blackwell, 1909 (Box 10, Folder 277)
  - Field, Theron R., 1894 (Box 10, Folder 277)
  - Fine, H. B.(*), 1900-1901, 1906 (Box 10, Folder 278)
  - Fine, J. B., 1903, 1905-1906 (Box 10, Folder 278)
  - Finegan, John J., 1899 (Box 10, Folder 278)
  - Finlay, J. R., 1894 (Box 10, Folder 278)
  - Finley, John H, 1920 (Box 10, Folder 278)
  - Finley, W. W., 1900 (Box 10, Folder 278)
  - Firestone, Forrest, 1905 (Box 10, Folder 279)
  - Fiscus, C. L., 1894 (Box 10, Folder 279)
  - Fish, Edwin, undated (Box 10, Folder 279)
  - Fisher, Frank R., 1909 (Box 10, Folder 280)
  - Fisher, George J.
  - Fisher, Herbert W.(*), 1922-1923 (Box 10, Folder 280)
  - Fisher, Irving, 1902, 1908, undated (Box 10, Folder 281)
  - Fisher, Nathan C., 1901-1902 (Box 10, Folder 281)
  - Fisher, Percy L., 1907, 1914 (Box 10, Folder 281)
  - Fisher, S. L., undated (Box 10, Folder 282)
  - Fisher, Samuel H.(*), 1889-1912 (Box 10, Folder 282)
  - Fisk, Frederic D., 1888 (Box 10, Folder 283)
  - Fitch, Grant, 1916 (Box 10, Folder 283)
  - Fitzpatrick, Keene, 1899, undated (Box 10, Folder 283)
  - Flanders, Carl, 1908, 1920 (Box 10, Folder 284)
  - Flanders, Henry R., 1894 (Box 10, Folder 284)
  - Flatley, Harry, 1911 (Box 10, Folder 284)
  - Fleming, George R., 1917 (Box 10, Folder 284)
  - Fletcher, Charles Leonard, 1891 (Box 10, Folder 284)
  - Flinn, A. Rex., 1913 (Box 10, Folder 284)
  - Flint, Joseph M., undated (Box 10, Folder 284)
  - Folwell, Robert C., 1913 (Box 11, Folder 285)
  - Fontaine, André, 1902 (Box 11, Folder 285)
  - Foote Boys' Club
    See: box 10, folder 262
  - Forbes, Robert, 1907 (Box 11, Folder 286)
  - Forbes, W. Cameron(*), 1899-1901, 1908 (Box 11, Folder 286)
  - Ford, Charles C., 1917 (Box 11, Folder 287)
  - Ford, H. Ward, 1894 (Box 11, Folder 287)
  - Ford, William H., 1889-1917 (Box 11, Folder 287)
  - Foreign Press Bureau, 1918 (Box 11, Folder 287)
  - Forman, Henry J.
  - Fortner, Louis B., 1917 (Box 11, Folder 287)
  - Fosburg, Ernest, 1902 (Box 11, Folder 288)
  - Fosdick, Raymond B., 1917 (Box 11, Folder 288)
  - Foss, Walter N., 1894 (Box 11, Folder 288)
  - Foster & Adams(*), 1917 (Box 11, Folder 288)
  - Foster, Cedric W., 1921 (Box 11, Folder 288)
  - Foster, L. W., 1907 (Box 11, Folder 288)
  - Foster, R. F., 1912, 1919 (Box 11, Folder 288)
  - Fowler, Nathaniel C., Jr., 1892 (Box 11, Folder 289)
  - Fox, Alan, [1899?]-1909 (Box 11, Folder 289)
  - Fox News, 1923 (Box 11, Folder 289)
  - Francis, Arthur W., 1918 (Box 11, Folder 290)
  - Francis, Charles D., 1902, 1910, undated (Box 11, Folder 290)
  - Frank, D. E., 1911 (Box 11, Folder 290)
  - Frank, Virginia Basnett, 1923 (Box 11, Folder 290)
  - Franklin, W. B., 1892, 1899 (Box 11, Folder 290)
  - Fray, Samuel, Jr., 1917 (Box 11, Folder 290)
  - Frazer, J. A., 1917 (Box 11, Folder 290)
  - Frazer, John C., 1902 (Box 11, Folder 290)
  - French, E. L.(*), 1907-1908 (Box 11, Folder 291)
  - Friedenthal, Sal, 1894-1895 (Box 11, Folder 291)
  - Fritsch, O. L., 1919 (Box 11, Folder 291)
  - Frothingham, Channing, Jr., 1913 (Box 11, Folder 291)
  - Fuller, H. C., 1894, 1902 (Box 11, Folder 292)
  - Fuller, Myron E., 1913-1915, 1919-1920 (Box 11, Folder 292)
  - Fuller, Philip C., 1902 (Box 11, Folder 292)
  - Fuller, T. E. U., 1903 (Box 11, Folder 292)
  - Fuller, Wilbur N., 1919 (Box 11, Folder 292)
  - Fulton, Henry, Jr., 1899 (Box 11, Folder 293)
  - Fultz, David I., 1909 (Box 11, Folder 293)
  - Funk & Wagnalls Co., 1894 (Box 11, Folder 293)
  - Funkhouser, Leonidas, 1894 (Box 11, Folder 293)
  - Futrall, John C., 1911 (Box 11, Folder 293)
  - Gage, Minot G., undated (Box 11, Folder 294)
  - Gage, W. B., 1894 (Box 11, Folder 294)
  - Gage, W. E., 1907 (Box 11, Folder 294)
  - Gallagher, William, 1894 (Box 11, Folder 294)
  - Gallaudet, Edson F., 1919, undated (Box 11, Folder 294)
  - Gallico, Paul W., 1919-1920 (Box 11, Folder 294)
  - Galpin, Henry Larned, 1903 (Box 11, Folder 294)
  - Gamage, Frederick L., 1899? (Box 11, Folder 295)
  - Gardner, Clarence, 1923 (Box 11, Folder 295)
  - Gardner, Robert A., 1919, 1923 (Box 11, Folder 295)
  - Garrett, Robert, 1917 (Box 11, Folder 295)
  - Garrison, Charles H., 1911 (Box 11, Folder 295)
  - Garvin, B. F., 1907 (Box 11, Folder 295)
  - Gass, S. J., 1916 (Box 11, Folder 296)
  - Gatch, Thomas M., 1894 (Box 11, Folder 296)
  - Gates, C. Halstead, 1889, 1892, 1894 (Box 11, Folder 296)
  - Geiger, Merl, Jr., 1920 (Box 11, Folder 297)
  - Gellatly, William, 1924 (Box 11, Folder 297)
  - Genslinger, Charles Henry, 1917 (Box 11, Folder 297)
  - Georgetown College, 1902 (Box 11, Folder 297)
  - Georgia School of Technology, 1907 (Box 11, Folder 297)
  - Georgia, University of, 1916 (Box 11, Folder 297)
  - Gerard, James Watson, 1918 (Box 11, Folder 297)
  - German Publication Society, 1914 (Box 11, Folder 297)
  - Gibson, Alex C., 1912 (Box 11, Folder 298)
  - Gibson, Harvey D., 1917, 1919 (Box 11, Folder 298)
  - Gibson, J. A., 1906 (Box 11, Folder 298)
  - Gidley, William L., 1904 (Box 11, Folder 298)
  - Gilbert, (William L.) Co., 1909 (Box 11, Folder 299)
  - Gilbreth, Frank B.(*), 1916-1917, 1919 (Box 11, Folder 299)
  - Gile, M. C., 1894 (Box 11, Folder 300)
  - Gilkey, Leon L., 1901 (Box 11, Folder 300)
  - Gill, Charles Otis(*), 1889-1894, 1907, 1910 (Box 11, Folder 300)
  - Gillette, C., 1896 (Box 11, Folder 301)
  - Gilman, Charles F., 1894 (Box 11, Folder 301)
  - Gilson, John L., 1917 (Box 11, Folder 301)
  - Ginn & Company, 1910 (Box 11, Folder 301)
  - Glasier, George W., 1902 (Box 11, Folder 302)
  - Glenn, G. S., 1903 (Box 11, Folder 302)
  - Globe, 1919 (Box 11, Folder 302)
  - Goff, Charles B., 1894 (Box 11, Folder 303)
  - Golden Syndicate, 1920 (Box 11, Folder 303)
  - Golf Illustrated (*), 1916-1917, 1920 (Box 11, Folder 303)
  - Golfer, 1899 (Box 11, Folder 303)
  - Goodrich, A. L., 1894 (Box 11, Folder 304)
  - Goodrich (B. F.) & Co., 1900, 1902 (Box 11, Folder 304)
  - Goodrich, Charles Cross, 1902, 1905, 1907, 1917, 1923 (Box 11, Folder 304)
  - Goodwin, Burnett, 1924 (Box 11, Folder 305)
  - Goodwin, William B., 1901 (Box 11, Folder 305)
  - Goose - Quill, 1899 (Box 11, Folder 305)
  - Gorton, Frank H., 1909 (Box 11, Folder 306)
  - Goss, C. P., 1899,1901-1902 (Box 11, Folder 306)
  - Goss, George E., 1911 (Box 11, Folder 306)
  - Goss, Ralston, 1920 (Box 11, Folder 306)
  - Gould, Alfred H., [1899], 1900 (Box 11, Folder 307)
  - Gould, Joseph F., 1915 (Box 11, Folder 307)
  - Gould, Norman J., 1919 (Box 11, Folder 307)
  - Gownley, Calvert, 1905 (Box 11, Folder 307)
  - Graduate, 1894 (Box 11, Folder 308)
  - Graham, T. W., 1906 (Box 11, Folder 308)
  - Graham, William A., 1902-1903 (Box 11, Folder 308)
  - Graves, Harmon Sheldon(*), [1893], 1899, 1903 (Box 11, Folder 309)
  - Graves, W. P., undated (Box 11, Folder 309)
  - Greenleaf Company, 1919 (Box 11, Folder 309)
  - Greiner, Hiram E., 1910 (Box 11, Folder 309)
  - Griffith, Frank L., 1920 (Box 11, Folder 310)